Register of the Christopher Temple Emmet Papers 1913-1974
Hoover Institution Archives
- CORRESPONDENCE, 1935-1974
  - Kingdon, Frank, 1940-1943 (Box 83)
  - Kingman, Woodward, 1965
  - Kinkead, Robert B., 1959
  - Kinnicutt, Francis, 1946
  - Kinnicutt, Terry, 1971-1973
  - Kins, Gloria, 1967
  - Kintner, William R., 1964-1973
  - Kiraly, Major General Bela K., 1958
  - Kirchner, John Edward, 1952-1959
  - Kirchner, Louisa (Mrs. John Edward), 1959
  - Kirchwey, Freda, 1940-1945
  - Kirk, Alexander, 1947
  - Kirkpatrick, T. C., 1950
  - Kiss, Sandor, 1957
  - Kissinger, Henry A., 1959-1972
  - Kizis, Mary, 1957-1960
  - Klapper, Paul, 1949
  - Kleiman, Robert, 1968
  - Klein, Alexander, 1955
  - Kleist, Ewald H. von, 1967-1970
  - Kletter, Miltoni, 1946
  - Klingelhofer, Albert, 1947
  - Kluge, Pearl, 1949
  - Knappstein, Ambassador Heinrich, 1962-1966
  - Knauth, Theodore W., 1952
  - Knigge, Baroness Louise-Sophie, 1950
  - Knight, Frances G., 1961
  - Knowland, Senator William F., 1950-1958
  - Knowles, Robert P., 1960
  - Koch, Representative Edward I., 1970
  - Koehler, O., 1947
  - Koesser, J. Horst, 1961
  - Kohlberg, Alfred, 1944-1959
  - Kohler, Foy D., 1952-1973
  - Kohn, Hans, 1949-1961
  - Kolatch, Myron, 1962-1965
  - Kopf, Hermann, 1968-1969
  - Korbonski, Stefan, 1958-1973
  - Kothny, G. L., 1946
  - Kotta, Nuci, 1959
  - Koutzine, Victor, 1959
  - Kovacs, Reverend Imre, 1962
  - Kovago, Joseph, 1959-1961
  - Kovats, I. Andrew, 1957
  - Kraditor, Abraham, 1957-1961
  - Kraft, Joseph, 1973
  - Kraske, Konrad, 1968-1972 (Box 84)
  - Krasula, Monsignor Stephen, 1950
  - Krebs, Max V., 1959-1960
  - Krebs, Rolf, 1947
  - Krekeler, Ambassador Heinz L., 1953-1958
  - Kriendler, Mac, 1969
  - Kristol, Irving, 1952-1974
  - Krock, Arthur, 1959-1963
  - Krone, Heinrich, 1956-1971
  - Krueger, Anna-Barbara, 1947
  - Kruger, Bettina, 1955
  - Ku, Cheng-kang, 1958
  - Kuchel, Senator Thomas H., 1959
  - Kuehnel, Adolf, 1947
  - Kuehnelt-Leddihn, Erik M. R. von, 1946
  - Kuhn, Charles, 1961
  - Kuhn, Irene Corbally, 1945-1960
  - Kung, Mme. H. H., 1948
  - Kupferman, Representative Theodore R., 1967
  - Kurtz, Father George J., 1946
  - Kutt, Alexander, 1965
  - Kyle, Alastair, 1955
  - Labin, Edouard, 1961-1962
  - Labin, Suzanne (Mme. Edouard), 1959-1962
  - LaFarge, Father John, 1944-1963
  - LaFarge, Oliver, 1939-1959
  - LaFollette, Senator Robert M., 1945
  - LaFollette, Suzanne, 1945-1957
  - Lahoff, Guenther, 1950
  - Laidler, Harry W., 1946
  - Laird, Representative Melvin R., 1964
  - Laitin, Mary, 1945-1946
  - Lambert, Darwin, undated
  - Lamont, Thomas W., 1940
  - Lamont, Mrs. Thomas W., 1946
  - Landauer, Carl, 1952-1968
  - Landheer, Bartholomew, 1947
  - Landon, Alf M., 1947
  - Landreth, Lucinda K., 1969
  - Lane, Arthur Bliss, 1948-1956
  - Lane, Representative Thomas J., 1959
  - Langer, Senator William, 1945-1959
  - Langkau, L., 1971
  - Larned, Jack, 1967
  - Lash, Joseph P., 1946-1957
  - Lasky, Melvin, 1957
  - Lasky, Victor, 1950-1959
  - Latham, Edward, 1956
  - Lau, Ching S., 1952
  - Lauer-Leonardi, Julie, 1958-1961
  - Laurence, William L., 1946
  - Laurin, Julia Chanler, 1946-1947
  - Lausche, Senator Frank J., 1959-1967
  - Lawrence, David, 1956-1967
  - Lawrence, James, 1957 (Box 85)
  - Lawrence, Justus, 1953
  - Lazar, Edmund I., 1962
  - LeBoutillier, Philip, 1941
  - Leddy, John M., 1967
  - Lednicki, Maryla, 1944-1947
  - Lednicki, Waclaw, 1944
  - Lee, George, 1940
  - Ledds, Carol, 1965
  - Leggett, Frances, 1946-1947
  - Lehman, Senator Herbert H., 1949-1958
  - Lehman, Mrs. Herbert H., 1941
  - Lehmann, Mrs. K. H., 1947
  - Lehrman, Hal, 1967-1969
  - Leich, John F., 1957-1967
  - Leiper, Reverend Henry Smith, 1946-1953
  - Lejins, Peter P., 1964
  - LeMahin, John, 1959
  - Lerner, Max, 1956-1970
  - Lessing, Harriet, 1946
  - Lester, Conrad, 1947
  - Lethbridge, Betty, 1958
  - Lettrich, Josef, 1965
  - Leuver, Father Robert J., 1966
  - Levine, Isaac Don, 1946-1970
  - Levitas, Sol M., 1945-1960
  - Levy, Adele R., 1940
  - Levy, Judge Matthew M., 1946
  - Levy, Mildred, 1948-1969
  - Lewin, Charles J., 1956
  - Lewis, Alfred Baker, 1947-1948
  - Lewis, Brackett, 1946
  - Lewis, Chester M., 1947
  - Lewis, Fulton, Jr., 1958
  - Lewis, Geoffrey W., 1953-1954
  - Lewis, Harry R., 1960
  - Lewis, Marx, 1951-1973
  - Lewisohn, Mrs. Samuel A., 1951
  - Liang, Hubert, 1945
  - Lichten, Grace M., 1949
  - Lichtenstein, Charles M., 1960
  - Lidz, Arthur, 1948
  - Lie, Trygve, 1946
  - Liebman, Marvin, 1955-1967
  - Liebowitz, Miss, 1966
  - Lilienfeld, George von, 1953-1961
  - Lilienthal, David E., 1947-1949
  - Limb, Ambassador Ben C., 1952-1955
  - Limbach, Scott, 1953
  - Lin, Mou Sheng, 1944-1946
  - Lindeman, Eduard C., 1947
  - Lindsay, Mayor John V., 1959-1966
  - Lindsey, Christopher, 1960
  - Linen, James A., 1948
  - Linz, Father Lester A., 1958
  - Lipis, Carol, 1962
  - Lippe, Princess de, 1953
  - Lippmann, Walter, 1944-1962 (Box 86)
  - Liptak, Bela, 1958
  - Lisagor, Peter, 1970
  - Listewol, Lady, 1956
  - Littell, Robert, 1947
  - Little, L. K., undated
  - Liu, Frank, 1946
  - Livingston, Dr., 1945
  - Livingston, Goodhue, Jr., 1952
  - Livingston, Robert Gerald, 1970-1971
  - Lloyd, Ruth, 1957
  - Lochner, Louis P., 1947-1973
  - Lochner, Robert, 1961
  - Lockhart, Jack, 1956
  - Lodge, Ambassador Henry Cabot, 1955-1960
  - Lodge, Representative John Davis, 1947
  - Lodge, Mrs. John Davis, 1948
  - Loeb, James, Jr., 1943-1947
  - Loeb, William, 1945-1959
  - Loes, Franz, 1950
  - Loewenheim, Edith H., 1940
  - Loewenstein, Prince Hubertus zu, 1973
  - Loewenthal, Richard, 1970
  - Lograsso, Angeline H., 1946
  - Lohrisch, Lothar, 1969
  - Lombardo, Ivan Matteo, 1961-1963
  - Lombardo, Joseph J., 1956
  - London Times, 1947
  - Long, Breckinridge, 1947
  - Long, Representative Clarence, 1968
  - Long, Senator Russell B., 1959
  - Longworth, Alice Roosevelt, 1946-1958
  - Loomis, Helen M., 1946-1948
  - Lorant, Andrew, 1957
  - Lord, Father Daniel A., 1941
  - Lord, Mrs. Oswald B., 1955
  - Loridan, Ambassador Walter, 1959
  - Lotsch, Dr., 1954
  - Lough, S. Allan, 1958
  - Lovestone, Jay, 1948-1971
  - Lovett, Robert A., 1948
  - Lowenstein, Leon, 1940
  - Lowery, Daniel F., 1958
  - Lowry, Reverend Charles Wesley, 1956-1959
  - Lubar, Robert, 1971
  - Lubersac, Count Raoul de, 1945
  - Lucas, Senator Scott, 1945
  - Luce, Ambassador Clare Boothe, 1940-1973
  - Luce, Henry R., 1947-1960
  - Lugonye, Vlayko, 1946 (Box 87)
  - Lukas, Edwin J., 1959
  - Lunau, Henry H., 1959
  - Lundstrom (C. J.) Manufacturing Company, 1946-1947
  - Lunn, Arnold, 1956
  - Luter, John, 1960
  - Lyon, Elsie Chung, 1949
  - Lyons, Eugene, 1946-1972
  - Lyons, Jean, 1945-1946
  - Maass, John, undated
  - MacAlister, Robert J., 1957-1958
  - McArdle, John Philip, 1946-1947
  - MacArthur, Mrs. Douglas, 1964
  - McCallum, E. J., Jr., 1960
  - McCarey, Leo, 1959
  - McCargar, James, 1956
  - McCarthy, Senator Eugene J., 1956-1967
  - McCarthy, John P., 1959
  - McCarthy, Senator Joseph R., 1953
  - McCarthy, Justin, 1958-1959
  - McClellan, Senator John L., 1959-1969
  - McCloskey, Representative Paul N., Jr., 1969
  - McCloy, Ellen (Mrs. John J.), 1952-1968
  - McCloy, John J., 1947-1973
  - McClure, Betty Brainerd, 1946-1957
  - McClure, Robert B., 1970
  - McConaughy, Walter P., 1955
  - McCone, John A., 1960
  - McConnell, Bishop Francis J., 1947
  - McCook, Judge Philip J., 1946
  - McCormack, Representative John W., 1956-1962
  - McCormick, Anne O'Hare, 1944-1952
  - McCormick, Fowler, 1958-1959
  - MacCracken, Henry Noble, 1939-1946
  - McCracken, James A., 1964
  - McCrary, Tex, 1946-1956
  - McCulloch, Frank W., 1949-1960
  - Macdonald, Dwight, 1961
  - McDonald, James G., 1947
  - Macdonald, Margaret, 1956
  - McDonald, Robert E., 1963
  - McDowell, Arthur G., 1951-1966
  - McDowell, Janet (Mrs. Arthur G.), 1966-1968
  - McDowell, Colonel Robert, 1946-1947
  - MacEachron, David W., 1973 (Box 88)
  - McEneaney, Kathryn A., 1946
  - MacEoin, Gary, 1963
  - McGannon, Donald H., 1960
  - McGee, Senator Gale W., 1959-1972
  - McGhee, Ambassador George C., 1968-1973
  - McGinley, Father Laurence J., 1958
  - McGovern, Senator George, 1963-1965
  - McGuire, Father Frederick A., 1952-1955
  - McHale, Edward J., 1957
  - Machrowicz, Representative Thaddeus M., 1957-1962
  - McIlvaine, Robinson, 1955
  - McIntosh, Millicent C., 1958
  - McIntyre, Archbishop Francis, 1947
  - MacIver, Robert M., 1945-1949
  - McKee, Frederick C., 1946-1958
  - McKibbin, George B., 1952
  - Mackehenie, Ambassador Carlos, 1958
  - McKisson, Robert M., 1970
  - McKneally, Martin D., 1959
  - McLain, Charles Albert, 1959
  - McLaughlin, Kathleen, 1957
  - MacLean, Betsy, 1940
  - McMahon, Senator Brien D., 1945
  - McMann, Renville, 1959
  - McNamara, Francis J., 1956-1964
  - McNeil, Hector, 1947
  - Macomber, William B., Jr., 1960
  - McQuade, Mr., 1963
  - McVeigh, Charles S., 1946-1947
  - Madden, Representative Ray J., 1957
  - Magnuson, Senator Warren G., 1945-1969
  - Mahoney, Jeremiah T., 1945
  - Makaroff, Vadim S., 1946
  - Makonnen, Ambassador, 1967
  - Malik, Ambassador Charles, 1957-1958
  - Malinowski, Halina W., 1944
  - Mallory, Walter H., 1946-1958
  - Maloles, Octavio L., 1958
  - Malsin, Raphael, 1956-1973
  - Manasse, George, 1960
  - Mandel, Benjamin, 1946-1971
  - Manice, Edward A., 1952
  - Manion, Clarence, 1970
  - Manning, Bayless, 1972
  - Manning, Bishop William T., 1947
  - Mansfield, Senator Mike, 1952-1958
  - Mansfield, Captain Walter R., 1946
  - Manship, Charles P., Jr., 1958
  - Manship, Paul, 1949
  - Mantikos, Joanne, 1967
  - March, H. F., 1946
  - Marcus, Robert S., 1940
  - Mark, David, 1971
  - Markel, Lester, 1967
  - Markham, Reuben H., 1947-1949
  - Marks, Henry, 1940
  - Marquand, John, 1949
  - Marsh, Representative John O., Jr., 1967
  - Marshall, General George C., 1947-1958
  - Marshall, James, 1949
  - Marshall, Colonel Robert P., 1947
  - Marshall, Brigadier General S. L. A., 1964-1966
  - Martin, David, 1946-1974 (Box 89)
  - Martinos, Brigadier C., 1961
  - Marton, Endre, 1957
  - Marx, Leonard, 1940
  - Marx, Werner, 1968-1969
  - Masse, Father Benjamin, 1956
  - Mathias, Representative Charles McC., Jr., 1967
  - Matson, Anna Walling, 1957-1964
  - Matsudaira, Ambassador Koto, 1958
  - Matsunaga, Representative Spark M., 1970
  - Matt, Alphonse J., 1947
  - Matthews, John J., 1946
  - Matthews, T. S., 1946-1947
  - Maull, Baldwin, 1972
  - Maurer, Herrymon, 1955
  - Maury, Reuben, 1947-1969
  - Max, Alphonse, 1960
  - Maxwell, Elsa, 1941-1946
  - Maxwell, Walter C., 1966
  - Maxwell-Scott, Marie, 1946
  - May, A. Wilfred, 1958-1967
  - May, Allen E., 1949-1952
  - Maybank, Senator Burnet R., 1948-1950
  - Mayers, Henry, 1962-1966
  - Mayor, Brantz, 1940
  - Mazeika, Anthony B., Jr., 1965-1966
  - Meader, Natalie, 1949
  - Meany, George, 1956-1960
  - Mebane, Anjin, 1955
  - Melady, Thomas Patrick, 1966
  - Mendershausen, Horst, 1971
  - Menjou, Adolph, 1959
  - Menne, W. Alexander, 1961-1970
  - Mennell, Peter, 1954
  - Menninger, Dr. William C., 1958-1959
  - Merchant, Livingston, 1963
  - Merrell, Marion, 1958
  - Merski, Major Henri, 1940
  - Mertz, Joyce, 1959-1960
  - Merz, Charles, 1946-1960
  - Mesirow, Mildred Harris, 1939
  - Meskill, Representative Thomas J., 1969
  - Mesnard, Andre, 1945
  - Metcalf, M. B., 1940
  - Mewhinney, J. S., Jr., 1952
  - Meyer, Annie Nathan, 1940
  - Meyer, Cord, Jr., 1949
  - Meyer, Eugene, 1944
  - Meyer, Mrs. Eugene, undated
  - Meyer, Frank S., 1958
  - Meyer, Hank, 1957 (Box 90)
  - Meyer, J. H., 1960
  - Meyette, Grace E., 1939
  - Meyner, Governor Robert B., 1956-1961
  - Michaels, M. M., 1941
  - Middlemann, Werner, 1954
  - Mieczyslawski, Aniela, 1947
  - Milbank, Jeremiah, 1947
  - Miller, David, 1965
  - Miller, Donald L., 1965
  - Miller, Gilbert, 1941-1949
  - Miller, Lawrence K., 1944
  - Miller, Philip F., 1958
  - Miller, William, 1958-1959
  - Millis, Mabel, 1948
  - Millis, Walter, 1945-1954
  - Millman, David, 1951
  - Milton, Mrs. Rockefeller, 1946
  - Minahan, Victor I., Jr., 1958
  - Mink, Representative Patsy T., 1969
  - Minkoff, Nathaniel, 1947
  - Minow, Newton N., 1956-1958
  - Minton, Robert W., 1960-1961
  - Miriani, Mayor Louis J., 1959
  - Mitchell, Arnold, 1946
  - Mitchell, Broadus, 1946
  - Mitchell, Clarence, 1970
  - Mittelman, Hazel R., 1949
  - Moench, Karl, 1962
  - Moennig, Richard, 1954
  - Moerdler, Charles, 1967
  - Mommsen, Ernst Wolf, undated
  - Monagan, Representative John S., 1963-1970
  - Mondale, Senator Walter F., 1967
  - Monroney, Senator A. S. Mike, 1959-1966
  - Monsell, E. H., 1940
  - Monsky, Henry, 1939
  - Montias, J. Michael, 1971
  - Moore, Alexandra, 1946
  - Moore, Anthony, 1950
  - Moore, Hugh, 1962
  - Moore, James C., 1961
  - Moore, James I., 1959
  - Moore, Paula, 1965
  - Moore, Walden, 1962-1970
  - Moore, William, 1957
  - Moran, Joseph J., 1953
  - Morawetz, Marjorie, 1945-1957
  - Morawski, Ignace, 1944
  - Morehouse, L. Judson, 1961
  - Morgan, Aubrey, 1944-1950
  - Morgan, Dan, 1966
  - Morgan, Edward P., 1966
  - Morgan, Edwin D., III, 1946
  - Morgan, James K., 1961
  - Morgan, Temple E., 1946
  - Morgan, Thomas A., 1955
  - Morgan, Representative Thomas E., 1959-1963
  - Morgenstern, Oskar, 1964
  - Morgenthau, Hans J., 1964-1967
  - Morley, Christopher, 1947-1949 (Box 91)
  - Morley, Felix, 1946-1961
  - Morris, Newbold, 1941-1945
  - Morris, Page, 1960
  - Morris, Judge Robert, 1951-1958
  - Morrison, Mary P., 1960
  - Morse, John H., 1970
  - Morse, Otis B., 1959
  - Morse, Senator Wayne, 1959
  - Morton, Senator Thruston B., 1959
  - Moseley, Sydney, 1943-1945
  - Mosely, Philip E., 1949-1970
  - Moskin, J. Robert, 1971
  - Moss, Senator Frank E., 1959-1970
  - Moss, Frederick W., 1941
  - Mott, Robert L., 1972
  - Mowrer, Edgar Ansel, 1944-1962
  - Moy, Ernest K., 1952-1957
  - Moyer, Henry S., 1964
  - Moylan, Edward, 1947
  - Moynihan, Ambassador Daniel Patrick, 1956-1973
  - Mueller, Albert, 1958
  - Muhlen, Norbert, 1950-1973
  - Muhlen, Ruth Berenson (Mrs. Norbert), 1957-1970
  - Muir, Malcolm, 1944-1958
  - Muller, Steven, 1965-1967
  - Multer, Representative Abraham J., 1967
  - Mumford, Lewis, 1940
  - Mundt, Senator Karl E., 1947-1970
  - Muni, Paul, 1949
  - Munro, Sir Leslie, 1957-1962
  - Murphy, Edwin R., 1961
  - Murphy, Senator George, 1959-1969
  - Murphy, Representative John M., 1967-1969
  - Murphy, Richard, 1960
  - Murphy, Robert, 1960-1973
  - Murray, Anna E., 1954-1955
  - Murray, Representative James C., 1956
  - Murray, Senator James E., 1945
  - Murray, Father John Courtney, 1956-1961
  - Murray, Thomas E., Sr., 1959-1960
  - Murrow, Edward R., 1947-1962
  - Muskie, Senator Edmund S., 1963
  - Mutual Co-operation League, 1963
  - Myers, Senator Francis J., 1947
  - Myers, Fred, 1956
  - NBC-TV, 1963 (Box 92)
  - Nabokov, Nicholas, 1956-1957
  - Nagorski, Zygmunt, 1970-1972
  - Nagy, Ferenc, 1961
  - Nash, Ernest T., 1952-1953
  - Nason, John W., 1957-1958
  - Nason, Robert, 1965
  - Natanson, Alexander S., 1940
  - National Information Bureau, 1959
  - Nau, Alfred, 1962
  - Nebolsine, George, 1957
  - Neilson, Francis, 1947
  - Nelson, Governor Gaylord A., 1962
  - Neske, Guenther, 1969
  - Neu, Kurt, undated
  - Neuberger, Senator Maurine B., 1961-1963
  - Neuberger, Senator Richard L., 1958-1959
  - Nevins, Allan, 1949
  - Newcomb, Elliott, 1955
  - Newcomer, Marion, 1943
  - Newman, Albert B., 1948
  - Newman, Edwin, 1971
  - New York (County). Court of General Sessions, 1951
  - New York Herald-Tribune, 1946
  - New York Post, 1947
  - New York Telephone Company, 1947
  - New York Times, 1946
  - Nichols, Doris, 1945
  - Niebieszczanski, Adam K., 1949
  - Niebuhr, Reinhold, 1946-1958
  - Niemeyer, Gerhart, 1959
  - Nikijuluw, Karel J. V., 1958
  - Niles, David, 1966-1967
  - Nisot, Ambassador Joseph, 1958
  - Nitze, Paul H., 1957-1968
  - Nixon, Vice President Richard M., 1951-1963
  - Noble, Mrs. F., 1957
  - Nolan, G., 1940
  - Nonnenmacher, Nicholas T., 1956
  - Norden, 1947
  - Nordstjernen, 1947
  - Norman, Dorothy S., 1949
  - Norrie, Christobel, 1946
  - Norstad, General Laurie, 1967-1970
  - Norton, Florence, 1954
  - Norton, George P., 1960
  - Nortz, Paul, 1948-1950
  - Notman, Arthur, 1940
  - Nott, Laurence H., 1957
  - Nouee, Countess Elizabeth de, 1973
  - Nowak, Kathryn Ellis, 1955
  - Nunez-Portuondo, Ambassador Emilio, 1958
  - Nurkiewicz, Ignaz, 1945
  - Oak, Liston M., 1944-1948
  - Oberndorf, Ludwig, 1950-1958
  - Obradovich, Milan, 1946
  - O'Brien, Father Joseph L., 1941
  - O'Brien, Morgan J., 1946
  - Ochs, Jerry, 1963
  - O'Connell, T. Bryon, undated
  - O'Connor, Basil, 1941
  - O'Connor, Edward M., 1956-1961
  - Octave, Helene, 1946
  - O'Daniel, Lieutenant General John W., 1962-1963
  - O'Donnell, James P., 1960
  - O'Donnell, Jerry, 1952
  - O'Gara, James, 1959-1962
  - Ohrbach, Jerome K., 1940
  - Okanaki, Florence, 1948
  - O'Konski, Representative Alvin E., 1945-1968
  - Oldham, Bishop G. Ashton, 1939
  - Ollenhauer, Erich, 1952
  - Olmstead, William, 1940 (Box 93)
  - O'Loane, J. Kenneth, 1946
  - Olsen, Arthur J., 1970
  - Olzog, Guenther, 1956
  - O'Neal, Michael J., 1958
  - O'Neil, James F., 1956
  - O'Neill, Hugh B., 1967
  - Oppenheim, Friedrich Carl, 1970
  - Oppenheimer, Elsbeth, 1953
  - Oppenheimer, Fritz E., 1952-1958
  - Oppenheimer, Harry, 1940
  - Oppenheimer, J. Robert, 1949
  - Oram, Harold L., 1952-1974
  - Orbey, Rauf, 1946
  - O'Reilly, Aileen, 1949
  - Oriel, Benjamin J., 1949-1969
  - Ormerod, Sir Berkeley, 1944-1961
  - Osborn, Frederick, 1940
  - Osborn, William Church, 1940
  - Osborne, Buckman, 1966
  - Osborne, James W., 1940
  - Osborne, John, 1946-1951
  - Osborne, Lithgow, 1957-1967
  - Osborne, Richard, 1957
  - Oslund, Genevieve H., 1957-1958
  - Oslyn, Jeanne, 1970
  - Ostermann, Ursula, 1951-1952
  - Ostertag, Representative Harold C., 1959
  - Ottinger, Representative Richard L., 1969
  - Otto, Egbert, 1963
  - Overseas Press Club of America, 1965
  - Overstreet, Bonaro W., 1961
  - Ozbirn, Mrs. E. Lee, 1961
  - Ozolins, Helga, 1972
  - Pace, Frank, Jr., 1960
  - Padilla, Ezequiel, 1947
  - Padover, Saul K., 1947
  - Paechter Henry M., 1958
  - Paley, William S., 1947
  - Palmer, Robert L., 1959
  - Panetta, F. J., 1947
  - Panuch, J. Anthony, 1950
  - Papantonio, Edward, 1956-1961
  - Parker, Virginia D., 1948
  - Parry, Albert, 1939-1959
  - Parsons, Edward Smith, 1939
  - Parsons, Geoffrey, 1946-1952
  - Pasztor, Thomas, 1958-1959
  - Pataky, Charles L., 1957
  - Patley, W. Garrison, 1941
  - Patsakos, Peter, 1966
  - Patten, Representative Edward J., 1970
  - Patterson, Eleanor, 1947
  - Patterson, Kenneth, 1952
  - Patterson, Margaret (Mrs. Robert P.), 1956-1962
  - Patterson, Robert P., 1946
  - Pauemann, Baroness Eva (Baroness Kurt F. J.), 1970
  - Pauemann, Baron Kurt F. J., 1970
  - Paul, Ella, 1966
  - Paulding, C. Gouverneur, 1944-1953
  - Pauls, Ambassador Rolf, 1970-1972
  - Peabody, Malcolm E., 1947 (Box 94)
  - Peabody, Samuel, 1953
  - Pechel, Peter E., 1962
  - Pecora, Judge Ferdinand, 1946-1947
  - Peeters, Paul, 1969
  - Pell, Senator Claiborne, 1963
  - Pemberton, John, 1967
  - Pennoyer, Robert M., 1960
  - Percy, Senator Charles H., 1967-1973
  - Perenyi, Etienne, 1957
  - Perkins, George W., 1953
  - Perkins, Roswell B., 1960-1961
  - Perrin, Francis, 1944
  - Perry, Ralph Barton, 1939
  - Perusse, Roland I., 1954
  - Petchey, Pauline, 1970
  - Petersen, Gustav H., 1957
  - Petersen, Peter, 1972
  - Peterson, Edna M., 1959
  - Peterson, Esther, undated
  - Petkovich, Dusan, 1959
  - Pettinger, Andrew, 1947
  - Pfaltzgraff, Robert L., Jr., 1969
  - Pfeiffer, Zoltan, 1967
  - Philbin, Representative Philip J., 1959
  - Philippa, Princess, de Braganza, 1957
  - Phillips, William C., 1947-1952
  - Picot, Ambassador Guillaume-Georges, 1958
  - Pierre, Andrew J., 1972
  - Pike, Bishop James A., 1958-1961
  - Pillen, Paul, 1939
  - Pilz, Wulf Ch., 1972
  - Pinchot, Amos, 1935-1940
  - Pinckney, Josephine, 1946
  - Pinsky, Gerald, 1968
  - Piotrow, Phyllis, 1962-1965
  - Piper, A. M., 1958
  - Pitzele, Meryln S., 1956-1962
  - Piznak, Michael, 1954
  - Place, Edward, 1946
  - Plumley, Representative Charles A., 1947
  - Podeyn, Hans, 1953
  - Poettering, Hans-Gert, 1971-1974
  - Pohle, Wolfgang, 1969-1970
  - Polanyi, George, 1956
  - Poletti, Charles, 1946-1947
  - Poling, Reverend Daniel A., 1956-1966
  - Pollock, James K., 1968
  - Pool, Rabbi David de Sola, 1946-1960
  - Pope, Gene, 1947
  - Popkin, Maxwell H., 1940
  - Porter, D. R., undated
  - Porter, W. M., 1958
  - Portnow, Solomon, 1940
  - Posadowsky-Wehner, Count Harald von, 1970-1973
  - Possony, Stefan T., 1966
  - Potter, Senator Charles, 1957
  - Potter, Neal, 1946
  - Powell, Bert, 1947
  - Powell, John B., 1945-1948
  - Powell, P. H., 1947
  - Praeger, Frederick A., 1972
  - Prendergast, William B., 1964
  - Prietzel, Nellie, 1946-1947
  - Prinz, Rabbi Joachim, 1962-1967
  - Procope, Hjalmar, 1947
  - Progresso Italo-Americano, 1947
  - Proskauer, Judge Joseph M., 1944-1947
  - Prouty, Senator Winston L., 1959-1964
  - Proxmire, Senator William, 1959-1971
  - Pucinski, Representative Roman C., 1963
  - Puckett, B. Earl, 1941
  - Puhan, Alfred, 1969
  - Pullman Company, 1946
  - Purdy, Frederick H., 1967
  - Pusta, Kaarel R., Sr., 1949
  - Quilleret, Pierre, 1942-1945
  - Rabkin, Bernard, 1960 (Box 95)
  - Radkowitz, Heide, 1972
  - Radoux, Lucien, 1957
  - Radwany, Emery L., 1946
  - Ramsey, Robert E., 1959
  - Randolph, A. Philip, 1946-1964
  - Rankine, P. Scott, 1947
  - Ranson, Carter, 1952
  - Raphael, C., 1946
  - Rauh, Joseph L., Jr., 1970
  - Rayburn, Representative Sam, 1957
  - Razey, Sylvia Wilcox, 1939
  - Reader's Digest, 1962
  - Reber, Samuel, 1958
  - Regnery, Henry, 1962
  - Rehak, Edmund, 1959
  - Reid, Fergus, Jr., 1969
  - Reid, Helen Rogers (Mrs. Ogden), 1940-1957
  - Reid, Ogden, 1951-1958
  - Reid, Richard, 1947-1948
  - Reid, Whitelaw, 1948-1957
  - Reif, P., 1940
  - Reifenberg, Jan, 1958
  - Reifferscheidt, Adolph, undated
  - Reilich, Frank J., 1946
  - Reinke, Harrison L., 1945
  - Reisin, Seymour, 1965
  - Renger, Annemarie, 1973
  - Rengo, Florence, 1949
  - Reston, James, 1966-1967
  - Reuss, Representative Henry S., 1963-1968
  - Reuter, Mayor Ernst, 1953
  - Reuther, Walter, 1944-1947
  - Revay, J., 1950
  - Revercomb, Senator Chapman, 1945
  - Revson, Mr., 1963-1964
  - Reynolds, Bruce D., Jr., 1957
  - Rhee, Syngman, 1944
  - Rhodes, Governor James A., 1970
  - Rhodes, Representative John J., 1967-1970
  - Ribicoff, Governor Abraham, 1956-1960
  - Richards, Augustus L., 1944
  - Richardson, Donavan, 1956
  - Richardson, John, Jr., 1957-1973
  - Richardson, Robert R., 1958
  - Richardson, Wayne, 1960
  - Ridder, Mrs. Robert, 1957
  - Ridder, Victor, 1944-1949
  - Riddle, Reverend Sturgis Lee, 1946-1973
  - Riddleberger, James W., 1947-1953
  - Ridgway, M. B., 1958
  - Riesel, Victor, 1945-1964
  - Riesenfeld, Victor, 1940
  - Riggs, Richard M., 1957
  - Riley, Representative John J., 1959
  - Riordan, William O., 1941
  - Riposanu, Pamfil A., 1960-1973
  - Ritchie, Ambassador C. S. A., 1958
  - Robb, Inez, 1957-1960
  - Robert, Oscar, 1965
  - Robertson, Walter S., 1954-1958 (Box 96)
  - Robinson, David, 1939-1940
  - Robinson, O. Preston, 1957
  - Robinson, Thomas P., 1963
  - Rockefeller, David, 1950-1971
  - Rockefeller, Mary (Mrs. Nelson), 1946
  - Rockefeller, Governor Nelson A., 1947-1962
  - Rodino, Representative Peter W., Jr., 1973
  - Roericht, Kitja, 1970
  - Rogers, William P., 1970
  - Rohr, Lizann, 1946
  - Romoser, George K., 1968
  - Romualdi, Serafino, 1961
  - Romulo, Ambassador Carlos P., 1955-1961
  - Rony, Vera, 1959
  - Roosevelt, Archibald B., 1946
  - Roosevelt, Belle (Mrs. Kermit), 1941-1964
  - Roosevelt, Dirck, 1950
  - Roosevelt, Eleanor, 1946-1958
  - Roosevelt, President Franklin D., 1943